jenabelle.com 2016-03-04

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY STATEMENT

\----

SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

SECTION 2 - CONSENT

How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at ciao@jenabelle.com or mailing us at: Jenabelle 10 Franklin Boulevard, Long Beach, NY, 11561, United States

SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

SECTION 4 - MAGENTO

Our store is hosted on Magento Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.

Your data is stored through Magento’s data storage, databases and the general Magento application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

Payment:

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read Magento’s Terms of Service here or Privacy Statement here.

SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

Links

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

SECTION 6 - SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

COOKIES

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

CART --> The association with your shopping cart.   
CATEGORY_INFO --> Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.   
COMPARE --> The items that you have in the Compare Products list.   
CURRENCY --> Your preferred currency   
CUSTOMER --> An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.   
CUSTOMER_AUTH --> An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.   
CUSTOMER_INFO --> An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.   
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS --> Stores the Customer Segment ID   
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE --> A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.   
FRONTEND --> You sesssion ID on the server.   
GUEST-VIEW --> Allows guests to edit their orders.   
LAST_CATEGORY --> The last category you visited.   
LAST_PRODUCT --> The most recent product you have viewed.   
NEWMESSAGE --> Indicates whether a new message has been received.   
NO_CACHE --> Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.   
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART --> A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.   
POLL --> The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.   
POLLN --> Information on what polls you have voted on.   
RECENTLYCOMPARED --> The items that you have recently compared.   
STF --> Information on products you have emailed to friends.   
STORE --> The store view or language you have selected.   
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE --> Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.   
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS --> The products that you have recently viewed.   
WISHLIST --> An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.   
WISHLIST_CNT --> The number of items in your Wishlist.

SECTION 7 - AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

SECTION 8 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at ciao@jenabelle.com or by mail at Jenabelle

[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]

[10 Franklin Boulevard, Long Beach, NY, 11561, United States]

\----
